

const quiz = [
  {
   question :'What is my middle name?',
   options: ['Emmanuela','Esther','Joy','Elizabeth'],
   answer: 1
  },
  {
  question :'What is my favourite color?',
    options: ['Purple','Red','Black','Blue'],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
   question :'What did I study in the University?',
    options: ['Medicine','Theatre Arts','Chemical Engineering','Electrical Electronic Engineering'],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question :'Which of these states do I hail from?',
    options: ['Ondo State','Osun State','Lagos State','Oyo State'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question :'What is my favourite Hobby?',
    options: ['Watching Movies','Singing','Twitter','Dancing'],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question :'What is my favourite Nickname?',
    options: ['Toyin Tomatoe','Blackie','Lepa-tohbad','All of the above'],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question :'What do you think I consider my best physical asset?',
    options: ['Lips','Body','Face','Legs'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question :'What do you think I may be insecure about sometimes ?',
    options: ['Forhead','Skin Color','Face','Nothing'],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
   question :'Who is my favourite person on earth?',
   options: ['My mother','My brother','My Bestfriend','My Boyfriend'],
   answer: 1
  },
  {
   question :'Which of these words best describes me?',
   options: ['Pessimist','Optimist','Realist','Idealist'],
   answer: 2
  },
  {
   question :'What would I rather drink?',
   options: ['Water','Soda','Yogurt','Juice'],
   answer: 2
  },
  {
   question :'What would I preferrably wear to a date?',
   options: ['Jeans and Shirt','Gown','Jumpsuit','Skirt and Top'],
   answer: 1
  },
  {
   question :"Which of these do you think I'm likely to get first?",
   options: ['Piercings','Tatoos','Surgical Implants','Braces'],
   answer: 3
  },
  {
   question :'What country have I always wanted to visit?',
   options: ['Germany','Canada','England','United States of America'],
   answer: 0
  },
   {
   question :'What is my worst pet peeve ?',
   options: ['Aggressive Interrupters','Slow Internet','Grammar Correctors','Constant cell phone distraction'],
   answer: 1
  }
];